

CONTACT ME AT

Charcas 3025, Palermo, Capital Federal.

com carlosarturomihanovich@gmail

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/c arlos-mihanovich/

Cell phone: 1565771195

Ghitub://ghitub.com/BladeRunner24

SKILLS SUMMARY

JavaScript

HTML5

CSS3

Node JS

React JS

Bootstrap

MySQL

Postman

Ability to work with people from different cultural background.

Ability to work under presure and with tight deadlines.

Client oriented (internal and external).

Lateral thinking.

E D U C A T I O N A L H I S T O R Y

Acamica - Full Stack Web developer Nov 2019 - July 2020 Digital House - Digital Marketing

U.C.A - Bussiness Administration 1997 - 2003

LANGUAGES

Feb 2019 - July 2019

English - Advance level
French- Basic level

CARLOS MIHANOVICH

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Full-stack Web Developer that looks to increase my experience in the web development world. I also have extensive experience working in business centers and providing services to international and national clients. I hope to use my experience to provide value in my next job.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer

Freelance | Nov 2019 - Present

- Developing the Chilean landing page and the Chilean and international web games page of the escape games company Enter the Exit.
- Back-end design of a REST API created to manage the clients, menu and delivery orders of a restaurant. MySQL was used for the data base and Node JS dependencies (Express, JTW and Sequelize) for the API development.
- Creation from scratch of a web app to share animated GIFs. Use of programming fundamentals and JavaScript to obtain data from Guiphy.com API. This was done working with asynchronic functions and taking advantage of the browser's native tools.
- Design a Podcast channel landing page. Develop the
 necessary functionalities to reproduce content, navigate
 between different pages and page different sections,
 check the compatibility between different browsers and
 ensure that the page is fully responsive and add the
 necessary animate interactions that are necessary to
 have the page working correctly.

Procurement Associate

ExxonMobil | Jun 2011 - Jun 2019

 Responsible for the administration of a contract portfolio. This portfolio includes IT licences, Software, IT consulting, Finances, Legal, Engineering and Staffing agreements that support company operations.

Oracle Analyst

Grupo ASSA Oct 2009 - Jun 2011

 AS400 and One World (Oracle) level one and two analyst. Responsible for the análysis and problema resolution of issues related to the administrative and security module. Main clients, Arcor and Johnson & Johnson.